[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Charles Darwin disgusted with while in Brazil during the second voyage of HMS Beagle?", "correct_answer": "Slavery", "incorrect_answers": ["Racism", "Animal sacrifices", "Live animal skinning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the mid 1980s Dr. Pepper became exclusively a product of the Coca Cola Company.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who composed and performed the ballad Goodbye Yellow Brick Road?", "correct_answer": "Elton John", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Bolton", "The Beatles", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Sally Fields character in Smokey and the Bandit wearing, when the Bandit picked her up on the side of the road?", "correct_answer": "A wedding dress and veil", "incorrect_answers": ["Short shorts and a halter top", "Only a towel", "A maids uniform"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor played Richard, the rich American whose wife is shot in the 2006 movie Babel?", "correct_answer": "Brad Pitt", "incorrect_answers": ["Ben Affleck", "Jack Schaffer", "Matt Damon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "While driving or walking down Kings Cross Road and Farringdon Road in London few people are aware that unseen beneath them runs which river?", "correct_answer": "River Fleet", "incorrect_answers": ["River Thames", "River Avon (Shakespeares Avon)", "River Rhodda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the diet of wombats consist of in general?", "correct_answer": "Plants", "incorrect_answers": ["Small vertebrates", "Insects", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Luke 6:13, Jesus called unto him his disciples, and of them he chose twelve, whom also he named apostles.  Which one did Jesus not choose?", "correct_answer": "Mark", "incorrect_answers": ["Judas Iscariot", "Thomas", "Thaddaeus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1643, a Native American uprising killed this unauthorized Puritan preacher of a dissident church discussion group, and pioneer in Rhode Island and the Bronx.", "correct_answer": "Anne Hutchinson", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter Cooper", "Richard Morris", "Roger Williams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Jewel Tower, built in 1366, is physically separated from the Palace of Westminster in London.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name of the U.S. state of Texas literally mean in Caddo?", "correct_answer": "Friends", "incorrect_answers": ["Vast", "Buffalo", "Wilderness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the US, what was the average street cost of a lid (3/4 ounce bag) of marijuana in the mid 1970s?", "correct_answer": "$15.00", "incorrect_answers": ["$20.00", "$10.00", "$5.00"]}]